The first time that I met Alice
she was six years old.
She suffered from 50 seizures a day.
Her clinician couldn't find where to operate.
This is why we developed our platform.
It analyzed the neurodynamics
and was able to identify the true
drivers of her seizures,
enabling the clinicians to eliminate all
of her seizures from 50 (per day) to zero.
Like Alice, there are 1.2 million people
in the USA
suffering from drug-resistant epilepsy,
and their only hope is brain surgery.
But half of the surgeries still fail to
stop the seizures.
We work with seven hospitals.
We validated the algorithm.  We submitted an FDA (application).
And soon we are going live with clinical utilization.
So Alice, like my kids here,
they are the same age.
And this is why I built FIND Neuro,
because every child deserves a healthy life.
Thanks so much.
And now it's my pleasure to announce the $25,000 award winner
in the Alumni and Affiliates Healthcare and Life Sciences track.
That goes to Noam Peled, FIND Neuro!